Eden, Philip Papers 6149
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Philip Eden Papers
1951-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Eden, Philip
6149
13 cubic feet
13 linear ft.
Papers.
5819034
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 30, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Philip Eden was born in Brooklyn, NY in 1913. He worked for the International Longshoremen's Association. He was the first economist to evaluate economic damages after someone is hurt on the job. He also worked as an economist on the first law suit where a wife sued her husband for part of his earnings. He prepared model child support schedules. Mr. Eden did a lot of research and writing on economic labor issues. Philip Eden died in 1990.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
5819034
- Subject files: Abbot - Christiansen. (Box 1)
  - Abbott v. Sangami '79, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alan & Allan v. Greyhound (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allred v. Daniels (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allred v. Horne Robt. Hillison (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Appiano '87, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aquino vs. Pepsi Co. 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Aspen Grove v. Trimont (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Asuncion vs. Virtusi, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Barnum, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Barnum v. Barnum Timer Co. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Baldwin v. Cutler et. Al. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Basalto vs. City of Lafayette (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Becker - '88 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bedell '87 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Beech (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Benway vs. Leonards Trucking Ronald D. Kappleman Esq. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bickel/Yannoh, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Berolgheimer Marriage of 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Birsner, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bishai vs. So. Cal. Ed. Gary Cripe, Esq. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Black vs, Matson (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bosley v. WSU (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Brooks '87, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Buckdruker Marriage of- (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Budden vs. City of Pullman (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Catillery '88, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Campisi (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Chan vs. Croron Moving (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Christiansen v. McInerney, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Subject files: Collins - Guyton. (Box 2)
  - Collins v. Liles et. Al., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Collins v. Marlloff (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Compilomgo v. Ford Motor Co. et al. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Coons v. Coons (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cozby '88, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cox vs. Gray et al. - Kenneth Branch, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Craveh v. City of Richmond (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Crook v. CSAA (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Currey vs. Herman et. Al. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Decker vs. Harley Davidson, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - De Leon, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Dunn - Tucker (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dodd v. San Joaguin Fishing Tool Co. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Eggers vs. Allstate Plywood - Gary L. Olimpia - Kelly, Leal and Olimpia (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Erdman (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Estrada vs. Skiller (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ezekiel v. Winkley (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Flaherty et al. vs. Dunsmiur Water co. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Flowers v. Humana Hospital (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Frazier v. Fibreboard (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fry, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Garvin '88, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Gaudry '85, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Gauthier v. Hawthorne (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Gilbert/Davila vs. Union Pacific Railroad (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Uport (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Assumptions (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Life- Work-Life (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Gonzales vs. Pan Am (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Gonzales vs. Regional Transit et al., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 11/13/83 Report, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Test (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Inheritance Tax Report (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Tax Returns (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Proj. of Past Tr. Of Ept. Accum. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Savings and State Accum. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Statistical Corroboration (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Prices I (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Gonzales vs. Pan Am (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Gordon vs. Carlson (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Gouch v. Santa Fe (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Mar. of Guyton (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Subject files: Hamilton - Larsen. (Box 3)
  - Hamilton vs. Laine, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Harper/Grosso (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Harrison vs. Tampax McNamara,Houston,Dodge et. Al. - William F. Houston Walnut Creek, CA (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Hasbrouck vs. TBXA Co. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Hayworth, Eva C. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hewitt v. Bell Helicopter Textron (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Hilliard v. Scheinman (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hindman (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Hear, Dean Lester see also Stoddard vs. Ling (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hodrick v. Westinghouse (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Hollie v. Alameda Co. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Howells v. Howells (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hunter v. City of Berkeley (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Leslie Hysell vs. Armored Transport, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hysell (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - ICA vs. Farmers Morrissey, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Ipsen vs. Lucas (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - James vs. Yacavan, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Jeffries v. Reardon (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Jenkins N.I.T. Trucking Gianquinto (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Jiminez v. Crown Fence (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Jenkins v. Knox (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Johnson vs. Chee - Bob Slattery of McNamara, Houston 1211 Newell Avenue Walnut Creek, CA 94596 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Kan v. Shuff (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Kapp v. Koppola - Paul B. Engler (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Kennedy v. Univ. Utah Med. Center 1983 MaKelvey, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - King v. Healy (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Klopfer (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Arbitration Letters and Miscell. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence/Miscel. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Exhibits (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Assumptions (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Sum (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Periods (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Partials (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Trends (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Factors (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Specific Data (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Append (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Koth (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Frank Lambetecchio (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Jan Lambetecchio (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Larsen v. Larsen (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Subject files: Legner - Murillo. (Box 4)
  - Legmer (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Lenos v. FEMCL (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Letelier (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Levison(Marriage of) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lewis v. General Dynamics (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Lewis vs. Lewis (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - McClendon v. Security Pacific (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - McDonald vs. Futorian (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - McKenna (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - McNut vs. Big West Drilling (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - McVay Marriage of Peggy M. Kagel (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - McVay Marriage of Peggy M. Kagel (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Malkin (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Manning v. De Angelo (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Macy-McCoy, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Martin - David Weinstein, Esq. - Russo, Weinstein and Bellia (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Mast vs. Mast - Marriage of Davis (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Metlenko (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Miller v. Gladman Hose (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Miyazaki v. McClellan (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Modir et. Al. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Mitchell v. Wash. Water Power - McDonald - Egan Cases (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Morris v. Mansville (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Morillo (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Subject files: Musial - Wyatt. (Box 5)
  - Murial, Margot (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Naber v. Crocker Nat'l Bank (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Contents (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sum (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - @ Periods (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Trends (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - N.F. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fringe Ben. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Nagengast (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Nagengast (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Mahas, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Nguyen (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Marriage of Northcutt(Goodwill of Prof. Practice (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - O'Brien v. Catton (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Osibon (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Padway vs. PT&T (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Palmer v. Horn (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Pelletier Bank of Agri. and Commerce(Stockton) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Pemelas (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Peshette v. Smith et. Al. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Potter v. Whitson (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Prescott v. Miller (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Price v. City of Exeter (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Prudeh (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Puhzaleh, Marriage of- (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Putnam v. Maxwell (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Ramirez, Patricia (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Racor (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Raridon v. Hyatt, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Randall v. Dietrich Trucking (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Ratcliff et. Al. v. Good Samaritan (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Rausch v. Chrisp Corp., 1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Readus v. Bud Antle (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Milne v. Ribero (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Richards v. Beal (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Rodriguez vs. Santa Barabara Cottage Hosp. (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Roggi (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Roybal v. Pac Bell (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Rudd, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Sahlu v. Pac Bell (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Sanders et. Al. vs. Napolitano (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Santos v. Kaiser (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Sargenti v. Rapid Harvest (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Schott v. Schott (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Wyatt/Kagel (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Source materials. (Box 6)
  - Indexes - CPx Liv. Costs Alaska (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Employment - Alaska (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture - Earnings, Trends (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Admissibility (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Anti-trust (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Arrests & Crime Data (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Administrative, Technical and Clinical Pay (1968 National Survey) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Athletes (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Auto Costs (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Full-time Annual Earnings (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Bartender (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Blind/Visually Impaired (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Bus Losses "Bus Interruption Insurance" (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Business Failures - Data on Dun and Bradstreet (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Budgets (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Canavin vs. PSA (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Pennock, Jean "Cost of Raising a Child" (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Common Population Growth and the American Future (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Child Raising Cost (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Compensation in 1970 Construction Industry BLS# 1656 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Constr. Laborer, Sacto. Co. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Consumer Price Index (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Dental Students, Survey of (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Depletion of Fund-Chart (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Death of Father - Effect on Children (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Case Records (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Child - to 12 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Student - over 12 to 25 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Marriageability - Combined Expectancy (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Dem. Earn. Cap (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Marriage - Dissolution of (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Business Losses (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Goodwill (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Legal Malpractice (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Uniform Statistical Averages (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Property Appraisal (Eminent Domain) (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Age Discrim. (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Price Discrimination (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Sex Discrimination (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Housewives and Mothers (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Discount Rate for Future Damages (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Dissolution of Marriage (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Divorce - Com. Prop Professional Educ. (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Divorce, Probability of CorresGraves 10/22/70 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - IQ and Educ. Test (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Employment Discrimination - Use of Statistics (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Salaries - SF School District, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - R.R. Testimony - "Average Remaining Years of Labor Force Participation" (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Fela Mailing, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Smith-Griffin Work-Life Expectancy Tables (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Fishermen (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Financial Ratios (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Government Employment (Pay Rates) (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - School Employees-Retirement System Calif. And Teachers (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Gov't Employment (Benefits and Reitirement) (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Retirement Systems State of Calif. (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Government County Employees Retirement Law w/ Amendment of 1963 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Source materials. (Box 7)
  - Appendix - no longer used (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Master Exhibits - not currently used (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Masters not current Append. And Exhibits (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Halpern (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Housing - Construction (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Homogamy (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Housewife (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Insurance Data (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - International Data U.N. states 1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Bank Charges on Investments - Interest Rates (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Job Tenure - Special Labor Force Report (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Life-Time Earnings (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Least Squares Method Explanation and Sample Chart (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Life Exp. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Long Shoreman (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Marriageability (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Mental Institutions Calif.-Costs (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hospital Earnings Data (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Mock, Marks and Smith Trial Book (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Medical Care (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Medical Costs Soar (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Drug Prices (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Military Pay and Pensions (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Military Pay and Correction Factor (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Military Pay Records (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Earnings -- Office Occupations (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Acctg. Clerks "B" LA-L Women Workers (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Calif - Selected Pension Plans (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Uniform Statistical Averages Paradise Airlines (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Cal. Prop. App. Standard Forms (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Potential Earning Cap.-Girl, non white- Lurie Report (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Plumbers (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Population (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Productivity - Unit Labor Costs (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Podiatry (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Corporation, Value of "Evaluation of Closely Held Corp." (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Pres. Value of Hope (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Professional Practices - Appraisal of Goodwill (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Rehabilitation - Blind (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Vocat. Rehab Experts (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Savings Data (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Wage Trends (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Bright-Moot Case for Seminars (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Masters - Fairway Marriageability (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Source materials. (Box 8)
  - Prudence -Moot Case (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Wage Rates-Service Station (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Soc. Security (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Social Security - Rates and Data June 1971 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Scope and Contents
    June 1971
  - Admissibility Overcoming Objections (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Social Security Benefits (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Spanish Surnames - Red Book (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Spousal Support (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Statisticians (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Taxes (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Teachers (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Testimony Sheet - Loss of Homemaking vs. Earning Capacity outside Home (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Todd v. Todd (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Women Earnings Data (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Vocat. Rehab (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Aver. Salary Per Member/Staff - All Public Elem. & Sec. Schools - U.S. - since 1900 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - College Teachers (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Wages (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Wealth 1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Wealth (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Women Workers (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Women's Earning Cases Data (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Work-Life Expect. (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Garfinkle (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Unemployment - Russ Nixon Summary, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Eden books and articles. (Box 9)
  - American Jurisprudence - Proof of Facts Second Series (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - American Jurisprudence - Proof of Facts Second Series (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - American Jurisprudence - Proof of Facts Second Series, Forensic Economics (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Inquiry and Recovery in the Course of Employment (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Statistics: A Guide to the Unknown (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Life Insurance:A Guide to Planning and Buying the Protection you need (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - United Nations: Economic and social consequences of the arms race and of military expenditures (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Estimating Human Life Values, Philip Eden (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Estimating Child and Spousal Support, Philip Eden (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Trials - Evaluation of Structured Settlements (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - American Jurisprudence Proof of Facts, Second Series (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - American Jurisprudence Proof of Facts, Second Series; Forensic Economics (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - California Western Law Review (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Community Property Journal (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Selling Millions with the Eden Method (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - The Practical Lawyer (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - The Practical Lawyer Vol. 10, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Material from binders. (Box 10)
  - Eden Manual: Folder 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Eden Manual: Folder 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Eden Manual: Folder 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Associated Appraisers of Earning Capacity: Folder 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Master Manual - Folder 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Master Manual - Folder 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Masters - Folder 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Masters - Folder 2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Untitled Binder - Folder 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Untitled Binder - Folder 2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Scott Bader Commonwealth (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Case files: Sheehan-Zuelke. (Box 11)
  - Sheehan vs. Schorle et al. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Sheehan 2 of 3 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Sheehan 3 of 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Shoua v. Jeffrey (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Slagle (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Solomon (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Song v. Filper (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Spahr (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Stadler vs. Gross - Riseborough, John, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Marriage of Stevens (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Stoddard v. LTV (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Stome v. Branch (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Sullivan Dissol. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Sullivan v. Sullivan (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Theone, Linda vs. St. of Ca. - Robert H. Morgan (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Paternity - Thierot/Ruisi (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Thomas v. Thomas (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Tolmasoff (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Vallejo Mobile Estates Rent Review (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Valley Grading Corp., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Vaughn vs. W.H. Tanklinpa - Martin H. Eber, Esq. Pratt & Eber (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Vista West Inc. v. Amer. Phillips Corp. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Ward vs. Smith (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Weger - Marriage of (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Williams, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Whitehead v. Frampton (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Whitney vs. Sabra Dental Products - Ronald D. Kappelman, Esq. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Wilberg, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Zuelke et. Al. v. County of Monterey (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Eden Deposition (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Writings: Social Welfare Programs - Safety Net or Spider Web? (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Writings: Murray's Losing Ground - A Dream Deferred (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Writings: Murrays' Losing Ground - A Saga of Scholarships and Politics (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Writings and publications. (Box 12)
  - Estimating Human Life Values (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Philip Eden - Writings, 1980 - Folder 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Philip Eden - Writings - Folder 2, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Philip Eden - Writings, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Philip Eden - writings, 1980 - Folder 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Estimating Human Life Values (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Volume 8 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Writings. (Box 13)
  - Inflation: Its Structure and Politics, Philip Eden, 1980: Advance Draft - Folder 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Inflation: Its Structure and Politics (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - The Work Process (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Articles by Philip Eden (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Philip Eden - Writings, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Philip Eden - Writings, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Human Capital - Course Materials (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Choosing Sides - Unions and the Team Concept - Folder 1 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Choosing Sides - Folder 2 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Vol.1 - Philip Eden - Folder 1 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 1 - Philip Eden - Folder 2 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Religion (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Folder 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Folder 2 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Folder 3 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Tax Studies - Folder 1 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Tax Studies - Folder 2 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Tax Studies - Folder 3 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Philip Eden - Writings 1951 - Folder 1 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Philip Eden - Writings, 1951 - Folder 2 (Box 13, Folder 20)